<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Take_Care</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="lbl_you_are_at">YOU ARE AT</string>
    <string name="btn_get_location">GET MY LOCATION</string>
    <string name="btn_start_location_updates">START LOCATION UPDATES</string>
    <string name="btn_stop_location_updates">STOP LOCATION UPDATES</string>
    <string name="thank_you">Thank You for contacting TakeCare.</string>
    <string name="intouch">One of our representative will get in touch with you shortly.</string>
    <string name="hourly_service">There are times when there are errands to attend to but you do not want to leave your parents/grandparents at home due to their physical limitations/illness/lack of knowledge of the city and the area etc. There may be times when your parents/grandparents want to go out themselves to the bank/to shop/for spiritual events/for little outings but you would rather have someone take them out to take care of them and at the same time give company. At all those times, if you have someone whom you could completely trust, it would for sure lessen your worry and add to their happiness by a great magnitude.You can call us on the numbers in Contact Us Page, at least an hour before the time from when you require services and we will be there to take care of your parents/grandparents at your doorstep. If the duration for which the service is required may exceed and is not fixed, we request you to mention the same when you call us. We shall not be responsible for the maid/driver/ others appointed by you and their activities during this period.\n</string>
    <string name="hourly_service_2">If yours is a planned absence then you can choose from our list of entertainment activities and add to this service in advance (not inclusive in the package and will have to be added).During all our visits for any duration we encourage teaching and helping the senior citizens with gadgets and technology and generate interest in learning new things that may be useful to them.We ensure that we provide best and premium services.</string>

    <string name="weekend_service">Taking weekend (Saturday- Sunday) breaks, short trips is no more a worry! Your parents/grandparents are now in safe hands. The weekend package is inclusive of a visit (the associate from Take Care will be with them from Saturday 10 am to 5pm); where they will keep them involved, talk to them, take them out, spend time with them etc. These hours can be split between the two days as well. The associate will however, stay in touch with them to cater to their needs during the hours not present in person. You can choose from our list of entertainment activities and add to this service (not inclusive in the package and will have to be added).You can call us on the numbers in Contact Us Page, at least five hours before the day from when you require services and we will be there to take care of your parents/grandparents at your doorstep. If the duration for which the service is required may exceed and is not fixed, we request you to mention the same when you call us.\n</string>
    <string name="weekend_service_2">These are the basic facilities that we provide.We can try and accommodate additions or requests as per your needs and availability of resources. You can call us to know about the available offers. All the services are charged per person. In case of couple registrations for services, you can avail special prices. All the services are charged per person. In case of couple registrations for services, you can avail special prices.During all our visits for any duration we encourage teaching and helping the senior citizens with gadgets and technology and generate interest in learning new things that may be useful to them. We ensure that we provide best and premium services.</string>

    <string name="weekly_service">Your business trips can now be their fun time too with our weekly service.The weekly services are inclusive of groceries (for the week, medical emergency and visits (Twice a week and the associate remains in touch on other days too. You can increase the no.of days of visit.);by our associates. You can choose from our list of entertainment activities and add to this service (not inclusive in the package and will have to be added).You can call us on the numbers in Contact Us Page, at least a day before from the day you require the services and we will be there to take care of your parents/grandparents at your doorstep. If the duration may exceed and is not fixed, we request you to mention the same when you call us.Please mention about the additional requirements like provision of food etc. (whether or not there is a cook to manage their meals or you would want us to take care of it) when you call us. We shall not be responsible for the maid/driver/ others appointed by you and their activities during this period.\n</string>
    <string name="weekly_service_2"></string>

    <string name="monthly_service">We are here for them while you are always there for them. We understand the unavoidable situations when you cannot be there with your parents all the time despite wanting to spend time with them. With our monthly service we take care of their groceries (managed by the associate visiting them and it only includes the regular groceries), medicals (This is inclusive of weekly checks if needed, monthly check. We have special geriatric packages just for Take Care and it is taken care of by Manipal Hospital), visits (twice a week- can be increased as per request. The associates however stay in touch with them on other days too.). You can choose from our list of entertainment activities and add to this service (not inclusive in the package and will have to be added).We offer DMIT at your door-step to help in gauging their interests and personality, for a pre-booking of three months. We offer DMIT separately under special offer for senior citizens.You can call us on the numbers in Contact Us Page, at least two days before the day from when you will be unavailable and we will be there to take care of your parents/grandparents at your doorstep.If the duration may exceed and is not fixed, we request you to mention the same when you call us.\n</string>
    <string name="monthly_service_2"></string>

    <string name="entertainment_service">It is very rightly said that age is just a number. You are never too old to learn anything. There are many senior citizens who enjoy particular activities and others who could not enjoy them earlier due to work etc. Our entertainment services include a wide variety of activities with experts to help your parents/grandparents with them, if required. These are all fun activities with a provision to have regular sessions too, in any of them as per the requests.You can pick up any two to be included with other services (hourly, weekend, weekly, monthly) and we will arrange the requested activities as per the availability. You can avail the complete entertainment service package and we will take care of your engagements throughout the month. The senior citizens can also form groups and customize their own packages with our help for activities throughout the month. There are trial packages available if you want to choose anything specific and try it for two of its sessions .You can get in touch with us to know the details.\n</string>
    <string name="entertainment_service_2"></string>

</resources>
