<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Take_Care</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="lbl_you_are_at">YOU ARE AT</string>
    <string name="btn_get_location">GET MY LOCATION</string>
    <string name="btn_start_location_updates">START LOCATION UPDATES</string>
    <string name="btn_stop_location_updates">STOP LOCATION UPDATES</string>
    <string name="thank_you">Thank You for contacting TakeCare.</string>
    <string name="intouch">One of our representative will get in touch with you shortly.</string>
    <string name="hourly_service">Be it a planned meeting or an unplanned emergency, a shopping spree or a movie, new in the city or a new area, avail our hourly services for all of these and many more.\n</string>
    <string name="hourly_service_2"></string>

    <string name="weekend_service">Your weekend get away or a business trip can now be their mini holiday or a fun filled plan. Get in touch with us to plan fun weekends for your parents/grand parents.Gift a weekend surprise and lots more.\n</string>
    <string name="weekend_service_2"></string>

    <string name="weekly_service">Travel guilt free. We take care of everything from their food to medical emergencies in your absence. Your trip can be a fun experience for them. Yes it is possible now. Get in touch with us and watch the magic happen.\n</string>
    <string name="weekly_service_2"></string>

    <string name="monthly_service">Be sure of happiness and well being of the senior citizen\'s of your family. We are here for them while you are always there for them.We will help you in taking care of your loved ones in the best way. We can together make second innings happier.\n</string>
    <string name="monthly_service_2"></string>

    <string name="entertainment_service">From weekly get together to gardening, self publishing books, we have it all. You just have to decide what you want to do and we arrange it for you. You can choose from our vast options and add many more.\n</string>
    <string name="entertainment_service_2">\nSome of the activities are:\n
1. Snooker and Billiards (at KSBA, coaching available)\n
2. Badminton\n
3. Swimming\n
4. Water Aerobics\n
5. Bridge\n
6. Crochet\n
7. Bird Watching\n
8. Eco Camps\n
9. Paper Quilling\n
10. Board Game evenings\n
11. Hydroponic Gardening\n
12. Yoga\n
13. Meditation\n
14. Photography\n
15. Painting\n
16. Knitting\n
17. Music\n
18. Foreign Language learning\n
19. Book Readings\n
20. Talks and Sessions (will be informed to the members periodically).\n</string>
</resources>
